Welcome to this section.
-: Bem vindo a esta seo.
In this section we're going to look
Nesta seo, vamos
at one of the most complicated topics in Python.
ver um dos tpicos mais complicados do Python.
So complicated in fact that I have not seen another course
To complicado na verdade que eu no vi outro curso
that covers this topic.
que cobre este tpico.
The topic is asynchronous development with Python
O tpico  desenvolvimento assncrono com Python e
and that means doing multiple things at once essentially.
isso significa fazer vrias coisas de uma s vez, essencialmente.
I'll let you know that you cannot run two things at once
Avisarei que voc no pode executar duas coisas ao
in Python, but throughout this section we're going to look
mesmo tempo em Python, mas ao longo desta
at how you can pretend like you do
seo vamos ver como voc pode fingir que faz
and how that can speed up your programmes.
e como isso pode acelerar seus programas.
Asynchronous development, as I said, is a complicated topic,
O desenvolvimento assncrono, como eu disse,  um
so throughout this section,
assunto complicado, portanto, ao
I'm also going to be referring you to a number
longo desta seo, tambm vou me
of other videos and other sources
referir a vrios outros vdeos e outras
from some of Python's developers themselves
fontes de alguns dos prprios desenvolvedores do Python
who have worked on making Python a language
que trabalharam para tornar o Python uma linguagem
that supports asynchronous development.
que suporta o desenvolvimento assncrono.
Again, bare with me.
Mais uma vez, nu comigo.
If you have any questions throughout the entire section,
Se voc tiver alguma dvida em toda a
ask away in the course Q and A,
seo, pergunte no curso Q e A,
and if anything confuses you,
e se alguma coisa te
and we will be glad to help you out.
A, e teremos prazer em ajud-lo.
I'll see you on the next video.
Eu vou te ver no prximo vdeo.